

Hello,

I'm Alfredo

https://alfredo-rosadilla.now.sh/

https://www.linkedin.com/in/alfredo-rosadilla

alfredo.rosadilla@gmail.com

Why hire me?

I've worked as a scrum master, team leader, UI interviewer (gatekeeper), and UI consulter for Globant Uruguay in the Matrix portfolio accounts.

I consider myself a person with great empathy, high productivity, and self-taught.

I love take part in big challenge projects.

I define the formula for success as follows: "Don't waste time, analyze yourself and take care of yourself, train your mind and be disciplined every day".

Skills

Leadership Strategic planning C4 Plantuml Monolith Micro UI's
Scrum Canvan Trello Scrum master A11Y Gulp Redux Jest
React Grunt Next JS JQuery Angular BackBone Storybook HTML
Wordpress Angular JS Typescript Browserify Material UI React Hooks
Redux-thunk Redux-sagas Webpack Css3 SCSS Less HTML5 Java
Styled components ES5 - ES6 - ES7 Mocha Sinon Enzyme MySQL
Jazmine React test library Node JS OAuth 2.0 Dynamodb Play Framework
Express JS PostgreSQL Spring Boot Framework S3 AWS Cloudfront EC2
Route 53 Beanstalk GCP Docker Jenkis English Spanish

Experience

Oct 2016 - Present

Globant

Dic. 2019 - Actualidad

LATAM - XP / Senior Web UI developer

I'm moving to Chile to work on this position. LATAM is looking to drastically upgrade their user experience through a digital revolution and I will be contributing to this effort.

Nov. 2018 - Dic. 2019

Quantcast - Share Services / Team Leader - Web UI developer

I traveled to the Quantcast headquarters in San Francisco on different occasions to participate in discovery processes, brainstorming sessions for new ideas and validated ideas for application architectures.

We got an incredible performance, taking on new responsibilities and starting new projects within the account, which led us to vastly exceed their annual growth metrics.

It was during my tenure in this project that I was certified as a scrum master. The knowledge acquired was put in the service of the team and we managed to refine and better manage our ceremonies, drastically cutting down meeting times while improving their quality.

Ago. 2018 - Nov. 2018

Quantcast - Choice 2 / Web UI developer - React expert

We achieved an incredible performance, which led us to grow vertiginously, increasing the number of developer positions and responsibilities assigned to the team. A new team was created through a mitosis process in four months and I was trusted enough to become its technical leader.

Ene. 2018 - Ago. 2018

Deluxe - IdentifEye - Web UI developer / Angular expert

Deluxe is a client with high code quality and user interface standards, with unique functions that give a great added value to their application. This project became a challenge that helped me to greatly improve my skills as a frontend developer.

Nov. 2017 - Ene. 2018

Grey - Grey Collaboration Team / Web UI developer - Angular expert

This job was one of my biggest challenges due to the great variety of projects and technologies that I had to work with. Many of these technologies are obsolete, which led me to stop working with this client as it inhibited my growth as a developer. During this time, my personal growth was more focused on managing the business side of the project.

Nov. 2015 - Oct. 2016

Altimetrik

Web UI developer / Angular Expert

I learned a lot about SCRUM and trained in Angular and Javascript lower level programming.

I was given a lot of time to train and improve myself, and I spent many days reading books to learn about Javascript. I expanded my theoretical knowledge base tremendously, broadening my understanding of functional development and laying the groundwork to learn about patterns and architectures.

The first books I looked into were in the You Don't Know JS series.

Feb. 2015 - Mar. 2016

Talleres Possa

Full Stack Developer

This was my first important client as a freelancer. The company wanted a personal solution to manage internal communication with its clients and the capability to synchronize their data with their clients' in order to make this communication smoother.

Feb. 2015 - Mar. 2016

Sophilabs

Web UI Junior Developer

This was the company I started my professional career as a developer in. My work in Sophilabs was the spark that kickstarted my career in the job I love. Given this, it was without a doubt one of the best experiences of my life.

Education

2019

Scrum Alliance

Scrum Master

2016

IAB Spain

Google - Digital Marketing

2017

Cocktail Club

Bartender Drinks

2019

Círculo Informático

Tecnician in repair, mantenance of networks and computers